(Leonard:)You promise?
(Penny:)I do.
(Sheldon:)And to show you that there
are no hard feelings,
(Sheldon:)I am willing to rub my
genitals on it as well.
(Amy:)Well...
(Theodore:)if we're rubbing genitals
on things, that's where I shine.
(Penny:)Little lower to the left.
(Penny:)A little more.
Is it good?
(Penny:)No, still hideous.
(Amy:)Well, I'm sure
at some point,
(Leonard:)we won't even
notice it's there.
(Penny:)Yeah, you'd think that,
(Penny:)but after a while it starts
(Penny:)showing up in your dreams.
(Theodore:)I think it brings
the room together.
(Howard:)Hey, tomorrow who wants
to paint the nursery?
(Stuart(off):)I'll do it.
(Stuart:)Why do you get to do it?
(Stuart:)I'm the artist.
(Raj:)Just because you're starving
(Raj:)doesn't make you an artist.
(Stuart:)Just because I look sickly
doesn't mean I'm starving.
(Bernadette(off):)Howard!
(Howard:)Guys, you heard her,
go see what she wants.
I think I'm in labor.
(Howard:)Oh, oh, okay.
(Howard:)Okay, uh, uh, uh,
I can do this.
(Howard:)We have a plan.
(Howard:)Somebody please
tell me the plan.
(Stuart:)I'll get the hospital bag.
I'll pull the van up.
(Stuart:)Meet you outside in 2 minutes.
Team Baby, go!
(Howard:)I love you.
(Bernadette:)I love you, too.
(Stuart:)Are we hugging or having a baby?
Let's go!